,Unnamed: 0,links,titles,domain,UniqueIdentifier,StationName,Location,articles,ners,locations
0,0,http://www.WSFA.com/story/37148991/14-year-old-boy-shot-in-mobile, 14 - year - old boy shot in Mobilewsfa.com -  (English / United States),WSFA,WSFA,WSFA (NBC),"Montgomery, AL","14-year-old boy shot in Mobile2017-12-27T23:28:44Z2017-12-28T00:45:58Z(FOX10 News)MOBILE, AL (WALA) -Mobile Police said a 14-year-old boy was shot on Halifax Drive Wednesday afternoon.Officers arrived at the scene around 4:15 p.m. and found the teen with a gunshot wound to the chest. Investigators said the boy was accidentally shot by a 14-year-old relative while they were playing with a gun.The victim is hospitalized in critical but stable condition.All content (c) 2017, WALA; Mobile, AL. (A Meredith Corporation Station). All Rights Reserved.","[(u'14-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u':28:44', u'NUMBER'), (u':45:58', u'NUMBER'), (u'WALA', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'14-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Halifax', u'LOCATION'), (u'Drive', u'LOCATION'), (u'Wednesday', u'DATE'), (u'4:15', u'TIME'), (u'p.m.', u'TIME'), (u'14-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'2017', u'DATE'), (u'WALA', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Meredith', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Corporation', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Station', u'ORGANIZATION')]","[u'Halifax', u'Drive']"
1,1,http://www.wesh.com/article/father-accused-of-shooting-4-year-old-son-to-face-judge-tuesday/14497906, Father accused of accidentally shooting 4 - year - old son to face judge Tuesdaywesh.com -  (English / United States),WESH,WESH,WESH-ORD (NBC),"Daytona Beach, FL","LEESBURG, Fla. --A man accused of accidentally shooting and injuring his four-year-old is set to face a judge on Tuesday.Herbert James, 24, faces aggravated child abuse charges.Leesburg police went to Stock Subdivision in late November after they received reports of gunshots being fired in the area.Officers said they found a vehicle parked at a home on Berwick Drive that had two bullet holes in the windshield.According to authorities, James exited the home and when officers began to ask him questions about the bullet holes in the car, he became uncooperative and went back inside the residence.Police said they heard gunshots from inside the home shortly after James went back in, and entered immediately to check on those inside.Inside the home, James was standing in his living room with a gun in his hand, while a woman stood near him with their 4-year-old son in her arms, according to police.Police determined that James' son had been accidentally shot in his torso when the gun was fired. Authorities said James was in his bedroom when the gun went off accidentally. They believe the bullet traveled through a closet wall and into another bedroom where the boy was struck while sleeping in his bed.""I feel just bad, it was my firearm. I could have been more careful with it."" James told WESH 2 News after the incident. ""It really was just a big mistake. I need to be with my son, I don't really need to be here.""","[(u'LEESBURG', u'LOCATION'), (u'Fla.', u'LOCATION'), (u'four-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Tuesday.Herbert', u'PERSON'), (u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'24', u'NUMBER'), (u'late', u'DATE'), (u'November', u'DATE'), (u'Berwick', u'LOCATION'), (u'Drive', u'LOCATION'), (u'two', u'NUMBER'), (u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'4-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'WESH', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'2', u'NUMBER')]","[u'LEESBURG', u'Fla.', u'Berwick', u'Drive']"
2,2,http://www.kmov.com/story/37147945/sheriff-17-year-old-boy-accidentally-fatally-shot-cousin, Sheriff : 17 - year - old boy accidentally fatally shot cousinkmov.com -  (English / United States),KMOV,KMOV,KMOV-STL (CBS),"St. Louis, MO","Sheriff: 17-year-old boy accidentally fatally shot cousinPosted:Wednesday, December 27, 2017 3:33 PM ESTUpdated:Wednesday, December 27, 2017 3:33 PM ESTCredit: KMOVWILMINGTON, Ill. (AP) - Authorities say a 15-year-old boy was accidentally fatally shot by his 17-year-old cousin at a house attached to a church in Wilmington.The Will County Sheriff's Office said Wednesday that the teens were in a bedroom in a residence connected to the Christian Faith Center late Tuesday when they thought they heard someone trying to break into the church. The sheriff's office says the older boy had a rifle retrieved from a closet when he tripped and fell.Officials say the rifle accidentally discharged, striking the younger boy who died at a Kankakee hospital early Wednesday. Sheriff's officials say detectives questioned the 17-year-old boy, who wasn't charged. Authorities say the pastor legally owned the rifle.Sheriff Mike Kelley called it a ""tragic accident.""Wilmington is southwest of Chicago. The boys' identities weren't released.Copyright 2017 The Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material may not be published, broadcast, rewritten or redistributed.","[(u'17-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Wednesday', u'DATE'), (u',', u'TIME'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'27', u'DATE'), (u',', u'DATE'), (u'2017', u'DATE'), (u'3:33', u'TIME'), (u'PM', u'TIME'), (u'Wednesday', u'DATE'), (u',', u'TIME'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'27', u'DATE'), (u',', u'DATE'), (u'2017', u'DATE'), (u'3:33', u'TIME'), (u'PM', u'TIME'), (u'KMOVWILMINGTON', u'LOCATION'), (u'Ill.', u'LOCATION'), (u'AP', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'15-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'17-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Wilmington.The', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Will', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'County', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Sheriff', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u""'s"", u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Office', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Wednesday', u'DATE'), (u'Christian', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Faith', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Center', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'late', u'DATE'), (u'Tuesday', u'DATE'), (u'Kankakee', u'LOCATION'), (u'early', u'DATE'), (u'Wednesday', u'DATE'), (u'17-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Mike', u'PERSON'), (u'Kelley', u'PERSON'), (u'Wilmington', u'LOCATION'), (u'Chicago', u'LOCATION'), (u'2017', u'DATE'), (u'Associated', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Press', u'ORGANIZATION')]","[u'KMOVWILMINGTON', u'Ill.', u'Kankakee', u'Wilmington', u'Chicago']"
3,3,http://www.wwl.com/articles/deadly-christmas-eve-shooting-was-no-accident-say-kenner-police," Deadly Christmas Eve shooting was no accident , say Kenner policewwl.com -  (English / United States)",WWL,WWL,WWL-NO (CBS),"New Orleans, LA","She said her boyfriend accidentally shot himself Christmas Eve, but Kenner authorities say the autopsy says otherwise.Police say 29-year-old Dominique Kendra Wix told them her boyfriend, 25-year-old Akoya Skeith accidentally shot himself while pulling his gun out of his waistband. But when Skeith died, the autopsy told a different tale.""After they looked at the trajectory and some of the other evidence that was there, the coroner's office disagreed that there was any way possible he could have fired the gun,"" said Kenner police Lt. Brian McGregor.""A projectile had entered the lower left side of Skeith abdomen and exited approximately three inches higher from his right torso,"" McGregor says the autopsy showed them. ""It was determined at autopsy that the location of the gunshot wound, the trajectory of the projectile, and the lack of marks from discharging a firearm at close range, that Skeith did not fire the weapon.""McGregor says when detectives confronted Wix, she changed her story and admitted she shot Skeith:""Wix claimed that on the night of incident, she and Skeith was in their upstairs bedroom.  Skeith had a firearm in his waist band and made an aggressive move in her direction with his body while standing across from her.  Wix first advised that Skeith's movement frightened her, at which time she retrieved her 9mm handgun from an end table and pointed it at Skeith and shot him.  Wix then stated that she only pointed the weapon at Skeith in a 'playing' fashion and that the two were not involved in any type of argument, contradicting her previous statement of being frightened.""Now Wix is facing a manslaughter charge.","[(u'Christmas', u'DATE'), (u'Eve', u'DATE'), (u'Kenner', u'PERSON'), (u'29-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Dominique', u'PERSON'), (u'Kendra', u'PERSON'), (u'Wix', u'PERSON'), (u'25-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Akoya', u'PERSON'), (u'Skeith', u'PERSON'), (u'Skeith', u'PERSON'), (u'Kenner', u'PERSON'), (u'Brian', u'PERSON'), (u'McGregor', u'PERSON'), (u'Skeith', u'LOCATION'), (u'three', u'NUMBER'), (u'McGregor', u'PERSON'), (u'Skeith', u'PERSON'), (u'McGregor', u'PERSON'), (u'Wix', u'PERSON'), (u'Skeith', u'PERSON'), (u'night', u'TIME'), (u'Skeith', u'PERSON'), (u'Skeith', u'PERSON'), (u'Wix', u'PERSON'), (u'first', u'ORDINAL'), (u'Skeith', u'PERSON'), (u'Skeith', u'LOCATION'), (u'Wix', u'PERSON'), (u'Skeith', u'LOCATION'), (u'two', u'NUMBER'), (u'Now', u'DATE'), (u'Wix', u'PERSON')]","[u'Skeith', u'Skeith', u'Skeith']"
4,4,http://www.wjcl.com/article/family-grieves-son-accidentally-shot-killed-by-father-on-christmas-eve/14508936," Family grieves son accidentally shot , killed by father on Christmas Evewjcl.com -  (English / United States)",WJCL,WJCL,WJCL-SAV (ABC),"Savannah, GA","CULLMAN, Ala. --An Alabama family is grieving after a 22-year-old's life was tragically cut short on Christmas Eve.Family members say Logan Trammell loved music and knew one day he'd be a star.""He loved writing songs, he was so, how that kid could come up with a song as quick as he did. He just has notebooks full,"" Logan's aunt, Tammy Jacobs, said.The Cullman man was killed in a shooting the day before Christmas.Jacobs said her brother, Logan's father, thought someone was stealing his truck that night and drew his gun.""He said he shot it up in the air and they kind of sped up and said he shot one more time toward, aiming toward the tailgate of the truck and the truck stopped,"" Jacobs said.""It's over 50 yards out there with a pistol and its pitch black, it's a long way and he said he just pointed and shot,"" Tommy Jacobs, the victim's uncle, said.Logan's father, soon realizing he had just shot his own son, frantically began dialing 911. Family members desperately tried to keep the young man alive.""I tried to save him and I just prayed 'God, help me save him, you've helped me so many times.' God had a better purpose,"" Jacobs said, through tears.The Cullman County Sheriff's Office is investigating the death.","[(u'CULLMAN', u'LOCATION'), (u'Ala.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Alabama', u'LOCATION'), (u'22-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Christmas', u'DATE'), (u'Logan', u'PERSON'), (u'Trammell', u'PERSON'), (u'one', u'DURATION'), (u'day', u'DURATION'), (u'Logan', u'LOCATION'), (u'Tammy', u'PERSON'), (u'Jacobs', u'PERSON'), (u'Cullman', u'MISC'), (u'the', u'DATE'), (u'day', u'DATE'), (u'before', u'DATE'), (u'Logan', u'LOCATION'), (u'night', u'TIME'), (u'one', u'NUMBER'), (u'Jacobs', u'PERSON'), (u'50', u'NUMBER'), (u'Tommy', u'PERSON'), (u'Jacobs', u'PERSON'), (u'911', u'NUMBER'), (u'Jacobs', u'PERSON'), (u'Cullman', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'County', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Sheriff', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u""'s"", u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Office', u'ORGANIZATION')]","[u'CULLMAN', u'Ala.', u'Alabama', u'Logan', u'Logan']"
5,5,http://www.wtvm.com/story/37154531/deputies-4-year-old-fatally-shoots-himself-in-brierfield, Deputies : 4 - year - old fatally shoots himself in Brierfieldwtvm.com -  (English / United States),WTVM,WTVM,WTVM (ABC),"Columbus, GA","NewsDeputies: 4-year-old fatally shoots himself in Brierfield2017-12-28T20:51:56Z2017-12-28T23:35:05Z(Source: Raycom images)BIBB COUNTY, AL (WBRC) -A 4-year-old fatally shot himself Thursday in Brierfield.Bibb County Sheriff's Deputies are investigating and say the boy found a gun in his home. He accidentally shot himself.Investigators say the boy was driven to Six Mile Supply to meet an Ambulance but he died before paramedics could arrive.Copyright 2017WBRC. All rights reserved.","[(u'4-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u':51:56', u'NUMBER'), (u':35:05', u'NUMBER'), (u'Raycom', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'BIBB', u'MISC'), (u'COUNTY', u'MISC'), (u'WBRC', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'4-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Thursday', u'DATE'), (u'Brierfield.Bibb', u'LOCATION'), (u'County', u'LOCATION'), (u'Sheriff', u'LOCATION'), (u""'s"", u'LOCATION'), (u'Deputies', u'LOCATION'), (u'Six', u'NUMBER')]","[u'Brierfield.Bibb', u'County', u'Sheriff', u""'s"", u'Deputies']"
6,6,http://www.wbrc.com/story/37154531/deputies-5-year-old-fatally-shoots-himself-in-brierfield, Deputies : 5 - year - old fatally shoots himself in Brierfield - WBRC FOX6 Newswbrc.com -  (English / United States),WBRC,WBRC,WBRC-BIRM (FOX),"Birmingham, AL","NewsDeputies: 4-year-old fatally shoots himself in Brierfield2017-12-28T20:51:56Z2017-12-28T23:35:05Z(Source: Raycom images)BIBB COUNTY, AL (WBRC) -A 4-year-old fatally shot himself Thursday in Brierfield.Bibb County Sheriff's Deputies are investigating and say the boy found a gun in his home. He accidentally shot himself.Investigators say the boy was driven to Six Mile Supply to meet an Ambulance but he died before paramedics could arrive.Copyright 2017WBRC. All rights reserved.","[(u'4-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u':51:56', u'NUMBER'), (u':35:05', u'NUMBER'), (u'Raycom', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'BIBB', u'MISC'), (u'COUNTY', u'MISC'), (u'WBRC', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'4-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Thursday', u'DATE'), (u'Brierfield.Bibb', u'LOCATION'), (u'County', u'LOCATION'), (u'Sheriff', u'LOCATION'), (u""'s"", u'LOCATION'), (u'Deputies', u'LOCATION'), (u'Six', u'NUMBER')]","[u'Brierfield.Bibb', u'County', u'Sheriff', u""'s"", u'Deputies']"
7,7,http://www.wlox.com/story/37154531/deputies-4-year-old-fatally-shoots-himself-in-brierfield, Deputies : 4 - year - old fatally shoots himself in Brierfield - WLOX . comwlox.com -  (English / United States),WLOX,WLOX,WLOX (ABC),"Biloxi, MS","NewsDeputies: 4-year-old fatally shoots himself in Brierfield2017-12-28T20:51:56Z2017-12-28T23:35:05Z(Source: Raycom images)BIBB COUNTY, AL (WBRC) -A 4-year-old fatally shot himself Thursday in Brierfield.Bibb County Sheriff's Deputies are investigating and say the boy found a gun in his home. He accidentally shot himself.Investigators say the boy was driven to Six Mile Supply to meet an Ambulance but he died before paramedics could arrive.Copyright 2017WBRC. All rights reserved.","[(u'4-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u':51:56', u'NUMBER'), (u':35:05', u'NUMBER'), (u'Raycom', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'BIBB', u'MISC'), (u'COUNTY', u'MISC'), (u'WBRC', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'4-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Thursday', u'DATE'), (u'Brierfield.Bibb', u'LOCATION'), (u'County', u'LOCATION'), (u'Sheriff', u'LOCATION'), (u""'s"", u'LOCATION'), (u'Deputies', u'LOCATION'), (u'Six', u'NUMBER')]","[u'Brierfield.Bibb', u'County', u'Sheriff', u""'s"", u'Deputies']"
8,8,http://wiat.com/2017/12/28/4-year-old-bibb-county-child-dies-after-accidentally-shooting-self-in-the-face/, 4 - year - old Bibb County child dies after accidentally shooting self in the facewiat.com -  (English / United States),WIAT,WIAT,WIAT-BIRM (CBS),"Birmingham, AL","BRIERFIELD, Ala. (WIAT) -- A 4-year-old boy has died Thursday afternoon after he got hold of a gun at family's home and accidentally shot himself in the face, Bibb County District Attorney Michael Jackson tells CBS 42.Jackson tells us the family lived in a rural area, in the 500 block of Cahaba Hill Road, and drove to a store to call emergency services. The child passed away at 6 Mile Supply grocery store.Sheriff Jody Wade says the family thought the store was the quickest way they could get to people to get help. Wade believes the family moved into the home recently, and didn't have the ability to access communications from there.Wade tells us the family said they had the gun stored in what they thought was a safe place. Family members were home at the time of the shooting; they heard the gun go off and found the child injured.The Sheriff's Office is investigating.","[(u'BRIERFIELD', u'LOCATION'), (u'Ala.', u'LOCATION'), (u'4-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Thursday', u'DATE'), (u'afternoon', u'TIME'), (u'Bibb', u'LOCATION'), (u'County', u'LOCATION'), (u'Michael', u'PERSON'), (u'Jackson', u'PERSON'), (u'CBS', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'42', u'NUMBER'), (u'Jackson', u'PERSON'), (u'500', u'NUMBER'), (u'Cahaba', u'LOCATION'), (u'Hill', u'LOCATION'), (u'Road', u'LOCATION'), (u'6', u'NUMBER'), (u'Jody', u'PERSON'), (u'Wade', u'PERSON'), (u'Wade', u'PERSON'), (u'recently', u'DATE'), (u'time', u'DATE'), (u'Sheriff', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u""'s"", u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Office', u'ORGANIZATION')]","[u'BRIERFIELD', u'Ala.', u'Bibb', u'County', u'Cahaba', u'Hill', u'Road']"
9,9,http://wkbn.com/2017/12/27/warren-crime-activity-police-investigate-child-with-injury-from-gunshot/, Warren crime activity : Police investigate child with injury from gunshotwkbn.com -  (English / United States),WKBN,WKBN,WKBN (CBS),"Youngstown, OH","Friday, December 221:30 a.m. - 1200 block of Harvard Dr. SE, Cheyenna Hastings, 23, charged with assault, disorderly conduct, drug paraphernalia and possession of marijuana. Officers were called to a car crash that happened in the parking lot of an apartment building. Police said Hastings, who had gone into the building, was at fault for the crash. When officers went to her apartment to talk to her, they noticed marijuana and pipes on the floor. She became ""belligerent"" and appeared to be under the influence, police said. At one point, Hastings slipped out of her handcuffs and punched the other driver, according to a police report. Officers said Hastings told police she was menstrual and threatened to relieve herself in the cruiser.8:50 a.m. - 1000 block of Woodbine Ave., a woman told police that her children were bitten by the neighbor's dog. The neighbor told police that the dogs belong to her boyfriend. A report was sent to the city's dog warden for further investigation.1:40 p.m. - 600 block of Eastland Ave., a 6-year-old girl was shot through the hand. Police spoke with the girl's mother, who said the gun accidentally discharged. Police said the girl's wound on her finger was minor. The mother hasn't been charged.Saturday, December 232 a.m. - 1600 block of N. Park Ave., a man reported being attacked by five other men at Rock Bottom Cafe. He said he was attacked after telling them to stop ""making fun of a dead kid.""3:42 p.m. - 400 block of Perkinswood Blvd. SE, Matthew McFarland, 33, of Warren, arrested on a warrant for an aggravated robbery charge.Sunday, December 242:07 a.m. - 2400 block of Parkman Rd. NW, a man reported that he was assaulted at the drive-thru of McDonald's. He said he didn't know the man who assaulted him but told police that he was intoxicated and in the other drive-thru line.3:33 a.m. - 2200 block of Beck St. SE, police were called to the area for a report of shots fired. An officer reported seeing a man in the area, who ran from the officer. Police reported hearing another gunshot and a .22 caliber revolver was found in the area of where the suspect ran. The suspect was arrested but later released. His name was not listed in a police report.Monday, December 251:11 a.m. - 500 block of Commerce Ave. NW, Tyreek Barnett, 22, of Sharon, Pa., arrested and charged with assault. A woman said Barnett assaulted her. She said Barnett was upset because he told her to sell her son's Christmas presents and she refused. The woman said Jenkins also pulled a knife on her and choked her, and her 11-year-old son broke up the fight.Tuesday, December 262:25 a.m. - 1200 block of Main St.,police were called to the area after a woman reported being shot in the back.Investigators then found 28-year-old Scott Rockenfelder lying across the driver's side seat of a vehicle near the curb. The woman told police said she was driving the car when they were shot. Police said there was a fight elsewhere, but when the victims ended up at the intersection of Main Avenue and 2nd Street, they were surrounded and shot. Rockenfelder died of his injuries.9:18 p.m. - 2200 block of N. Feederle Dr. SE, Trumbull Metropolitan Housing Authority officers were called to check on a woman who was suspected of using drugs. Police said when officers arrived, they found a woman holding her 11-month-old child, who appeared to have several bruises. She told police that the child fell down the steps. Police said the apartment was deplorable and was not safe for the child. The child was taken to the hospital, and a report was sent to Children Services.Wednesday, December 275:45 a.m. - 400 block of York Ave. SW, James Chambers, 51, arrested and charged with felonious assault. A woman told police that Chambers held a knife to her throat after an argument about her going to the methadone clinic. Police said the woman had a cut on her neck, but it did not appear to require medical attention.Disclaimer: These reports don't represent all calls made to the Warren City Police Department. This public information was provided in reports from the Warren City Police Department. Items reflect charges filed, not convictions.Looking for more crime activity? See more communities here:.","[(u'Friday', u'DATE'), (u',', u'DATE'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'221:30', u'TIME'), (u'a.m.', u'TIME'), (u'1200', u'DATE'), (u'Cheyenna', u'PERSON'), (u'Hastings', u'PERSON'), (u'23', u'NUMBER'), (u'Hastings', u'PERSON'), (u'one', u'NUMBER'), (u'Hastings', u'PERSON'), (u'Hastings', u'PERSON'), (u'.8:50', u'TIME'), (u'a.m.', u'TIME'), (u'1000', u'DATE'), (u'Woodbine', u'LOCATION'), (u'Ave.', u'LOCATION'), (u'.1:40', u'TIME'), (u'p.m.', u'TIME'), (u'600', u'NUMBER'), (u'Eastland', u'LOCATION'), (u'Ave.', u'LOCATION'), (u'6-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'232', u'NUMBER'), (u'1600', u'DATE'), (u'N.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Park', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Ave.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'five', u'NUMBER'), (u'Rock', u'LOCATION'), (u'Bottom', u'LOCATION'), (u'Cafe', u'LOCATION'), (u'3:42', u'TIME'), (u'p.m.', u'TIME'), (u'400', u'NUMBER'), (u'Perkinswood', u'LOCATION'), (u'Blvd.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Matthew', u'PERSON'), (u'McFarland', u'PERSON'), (u'33', u'NUMBER'), (u'Warren', u'PERSON'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'242:07', u'TIME'), (u'a.m.', u'TIME'), (u'2400', u'DATE'), (u'NW', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'McDonald', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u""'s"", u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'.3:33', u'TIME'), (u'a.m.', u'TIME'), (u'2200', u'DATE'), (u'Beck', u'LOCATION'), (u'St.', u'LOCATION'), (u'SE', u'LOCATION'), (u'.22', u'NUMBER'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'251:11', u'TIME'), (u'a.m.', u'TIME'), (u'500', u'NUMBER'), (u'Commerce', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Ave.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'NW', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Tyreek', u'PERSON'), (u'Barnett', u'PERSON'), (u'22', u'NUMBER'), (u'Sharon', u'PERSON'), (u'Pa.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Barnett', u'PERSON'), (u'Barnett', u'PERSON'), (u'Christmas', u'DATE'), (u'Jenkins', u'PERSON'), (u'11-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'262:25', u'NUMBER'), (u'1200', u'DATE'), (u'28-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Scott', u'PERSON'), (u'Rockenfelder', u'PERSON'), (u'2nd', u'ORDINAL'), (u'Rockenfelder', u'PERSON'), (u'.9:18', u'TIME'), (u'p.m.', u'TIME'), (u'2200', u'DATE'), (u'Trumbull', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Metropolitan', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Housing', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Authority', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'11-month-old', u'DURATION'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'275:45', u'TIME'), (u'a.m.', u'TIME'), (u'400', u'NUMBER'), (u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'Chambers', u'PERSON'), (u'51', u'NUMBER'), (u'Chambers', u'PERSON'), (u'Warren', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'City', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Police', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Department', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Warren', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'City', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Police', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Department', u'ORGANIZATION')]","[u'Woodbine', u'Ave.', u'Eastland', u'Ave.', u'Rock', u'Bottom', u'Cafe', u'Perkinswood', u'Blvd.', u'Beck', u'St.', u'SE', u'Pa.']"
10,10,http://www.kvoa.com/story/37155143/court-records-man-accidentally-shoots-and-kills-father, Court records : Man accidentally shoots and kills father - KVOA | KVOA . comkvoa.com -  (English / United States),KVOA,KVOA,KVOA (NBC),"Tucson, AZ","Court records: Man accidentally shoots and kills fatherPosted:Thursday, December 28, 2017 5:32 PM ESTUpdated:Thursday, December 28, 2017 5:35 PM ESTTUCSON - A man is dead after his son appears to have accidentally shot him, according to court records.A 41-year-old man called 911 on Dec. 22 at about 4 a.m. He said he accidentally shot his father at Le Mirage Apartments near Thornydale Road and Linda Vista Boulevard, according to a warrant filed by the Pima County Sheriff's Department.The son told detectives they both woke up to get ready for work.""[The son] picked [the handgun] up and handed it to his father. [The son] said when his father grabbed the gun, it went off while still in his hand,"" according to the records.The man was dead on the living room floor with what appeared to be a single wound to the chest.Detectives are investigating the case and working with the Pima County Attorney's Office. No charges have been filed at this time, according to Deputy Ryan Inglett.","[(u'Thursday', u'DATE'), (u',', u'TIME'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'28', u'DATE'), (u',', u'DATE'), (u'2017', u'DATE'), (u'5:32', u'TIME'), (u'PM', u'TIME'), (u'Thursday', u'DATE'), (u',', u'TIME'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'28', u'DATE'), (u',', u'DATE'), (u'2017', u'DATE'), (u'5:35', u'TIME'), (u'PM', u'TIME'), (u'41-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'911', u'NUMBER'), (u'Dec.', u'DATE'), (u'22', u'DATE'), (u'at', u'TIME'), (u'about', u'TIME'), (u'4', u'TIME'), (u'a.m.', u'TIME'), (u'Thornydale', u'LOCATION'), (u'Road', u'LOCATION'), (u'Linda', u'LOCATION'), (u'Vista', u'LOCATION'), (u'Boulevard', u'LOCATION'), (u'Pima', u'LOCATION'), (u'County', u'LOCATION'), (u'Pima', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'County', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Attorney', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u""'s"", u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Office', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Ryan', u'PERSON'), (u'Inglett', u'PERSON')]","[u'Thornydale', u'Road', u'Linda', u'Vista', u'Boulevard', u'Pima', u'County']"
11,11,http://www.wowt.com/content/news/Accidental-shooting-reported-at-indoor-range--467038373.html, Accidental shooting reported at indoor rangewowt.com -  (English / United States),WOWT,WOWT,WOWT (NBC),"Omaha, NE","OMAHA, Neb. (WOWT) --Authorities say a former Omaha police officer accidentally shot himself at a gun range Saturday.The victim, 70-year-old Langston Farrish, was an Omaha Police Officer until 1998.The shooting reportedly happened Saturday at Inner 10 Weapons and Training in north Omaha. Police say video at the indoor range shows the shooting was accidental.Farrish was taken to Nebraska Medical Center, where he had surgery. As of Wednesday night, he is in fair condition.","[(u'OMAHA', u'LOCATION'), (u'Neb.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Omaha', u'LOCATION'), (u'70-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Langston', u'PERSON'), (u'Farrish', u'PERSON'), (u'Omaha', u'LOCATION'), (u'1998', u'DATE'), (u'Saturday', u'DATE'), (u'10', u'NUMBER'), (u'Omaha', u'LOCATION'), (u'Nebraska', u'LOCATION'), (u'Medical', u'LOCATION'), (u'Center', u'LOCATION'), (u'Wednesday', u'DATE'), (u'night', u'TIME')]","[u'OMAHA', u'Neb.', u'Omaha', u'Omaha', u'Omaha', u'Nebraska', u'Medical', u'Center']"
12,12,http://www.wcnc.com/news/features/2017-in-review-top-10-photo-galleries/501731619, 2017 in review : Top 10 photo gallerieswcnc.com -  (English / United States),WCNC,WCNC,WCNC-CLT (NBC),"Charlotte, NC","Mitzi Morris, WCNC8:40 AM. EST December 28, 2017Here are 2017's most memorable moments in pictures:Last year, Charlotte's number one photo gallery was Carolina Panther Greg Olsen's Waxhaw home going on the market. This year, a different house up for sale took the title: the Lake Norman home where several scenes from Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby were filmed.The 9,802 sq. foot home was listed in September at $4,200,000, with five bedrooms, six full baths and three partial baths. It was built in 2002 and stood on 1.3 acres. The home was in a private gated community in Cornelius.WCNCToward the end of the first week in January, the Charlotte-area was under a winter storm warning.The Charlotte Department of Transportation rolled out most of its fleet of snow plows to treat the roads ahead of the storm. At Charlotte Douglas International Airport, CDOT pre-treated all the roads in the area, including Josh Birmingham Parkway.Charlotte-Mecklenburg Schools canceled activities for January 6 and the weekend. However, school operated on a normal schedule on Friday.In October, authorities in Georgia confirmed a two-week-old baby discovered in the woods died from blunt force trauma to the head. The baby, found by a search party in Newton County, was identified as Caliyah McNabb.Her father, Christopher McNabb, was charged with malice murder, felony murder, aggravated battery and concealing a death.A warrant said McNabb wrapped his daughter's body in a t-shirt and blanket before putting her in a drawstring bag and hiding her in the woods.(Photo: Coldwell Banker Real Estate)A mansion in the middle of nowhere went on the market in June for less than $140,000.The Read Mansion was built in 1914 in Winner, South Dakota, and no one really knows why. Local legend includes an account of multiple houses being moved to the area and joined together.After five months on the market, hundreds of phone calls from all over the U.S. and around the globe, sight-unseen cash offers, bizarre questions and nearly daily emails, the mansion sold to  the managers of the local airport for about $119,000.13-year-old Malachi Hemphill died after shooting himself on Instagram Live. His mother said the shooting was an accident.In April, more than a dozen people were watching Malachi Nasir Hemphill live on Instagram in Forest Park, Georgia when he accidentally shot himself in the head.His mother said her 13-year-old son was attempting to put a clip in the gun when it went off. The boy later died at a local hospital.Police began investigating where Hemphill got the Hi-Point 9 mm pistol. No signs pointed to the shooting being suicide, investigators said.A man was credited with helping capture a wanted Kershaw County, South Carolina suspect in August.Deputies said 21-year-old Christopher Cravets had been on the run for several hours when Charles Belcher found him in the back of an SUV in carport. Belcher was visiting his girlfriend at the time.""I came out to check the green Explorer and saw somebody in the back and I just pulled my weapon and ordered him out of the vehicle and made him get on the ground until the cops got here,"" Belcher said.As you click through this gallery. you see the sports logo first, followed by an explainer of the hidden image.In what was called one of the largest indictments ever handed down in the Western District of North Carolina, 83 alleged members of the United Blood Nation gang were charged with a slew of crimes in May.The crimes included racketeering and murder, as well as dealing drugs and guns. According to the 163-page indictment, the criminal activity started in or around September 2009 and continued through 2017.A number of those indicted were accused of bank fraud, wire fraud, and aggravated identity theft.Carolinians had to clean up after Hurricane Irma roared through the region in September.After moving north through Georgia, the National Hurricane Center downgraded Irma to a post-tropical cyclone. Charlotte saw wind gusts up to 45 mph, while Grandfather Mountain saw the strongest gusts at 62 mph.At least 18 school districts in the Charlotte area were delayed due to widespread power outages. In Cleveland County, three schools were forced to close after crews were unable to restore power in time for classes.Tourists watch the 'Old Faithful' geyser which erupts on average every 90 minutes in the Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming on June 1, 2011. Credit: MARK RALSTON/AFP/Getty Images(Photo: MARK RALSTON, 2011 AFP)Established on March 1, 1872, Yellowstone National Park has the distinct honor of being the world's first national park.Last year, more than 4 million people visited the park that spans more than 3,472 square miles over three states - Idaho, Montana and (mostly) Wyoming.With such a massive size and varied terrain, there's plenty to do in Yellowstone, and plenty for kids, too.(c) 2017 WCNC.COM","[(u'Mitzi', u'PERSON'), (u'Morris', u'PERSON'), (u':40', u'NUMBER'), (u'December', u'DATE'), (u'28', u'DATE'), (u'2017', u'DATE'), (u'Last', u'DATE'), (u'year', u'DATE'), (u'Charlotte', u'LOCATION'), (u'one', u'NUMBER'), (u'Carolina', u'PERSON'), (u'Panther', u'PERSON'), (u'Greg', u'PERSON'), (u'Olsen', u'PERSON'), (u'Waxhaw', u'LOCATION'), (u'This', u'DATE'), (u'year', u'DATE'), (u'Lake', u'LOCATION'), (u'Norman', u'LOCATION'), (u'Talladega', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Nights', u'TIME'), (u'Ricky', u'PERSON'), (u'Bobby', u'PERSON'), (u'9,802', u'NUMBER'), (u'September', u'DATE'), (u'$', u'MONEY'), (u'4,200,000', u'MONEY'), (u'five', u'NUMBER'), (u'six', u'NUMBER'), (u'three', u'NUMBER'), (u'2002', u'DATE'), (u'1.3', u'NUMBER'), (u'the', u'DATE'), (u'end', u'DATE'), (u'of', u'DATE'), (u'the', u'DATE'), (u'first', u'DATE'), (u'week', u'DATE'), (u'in', u'DATE'), (u'January', u'DATE'), (u'Charlotte-area', u'MISC'), (u'winter', u'DATE'), (u'Charlotte', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Department', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'of', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Transportation', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Charlotte', u'LOCATION'), (u'Douglas', u'LOCATION'), (u'International', u'LOCATION'), (u'Airport', u'LOCATION'), (u'CDOT', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Josh', u'PERSON'), (u'Birmingham', u'PERSON'), (u'January', u'DATE'), (u'6', u'DATE'), (u'the', u'DATE'), (u'weekend', u'DATE'), (u'October', u'DATE'), (u'Georgia', u'LOCATION'), (u'two-week-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Newton', u'LOCATION'), (u'County', u'LOCATION'), (u'Christopher', u'PERSON'), (u'McNabb', u'PERSON'), (u'McNabb', u'PERSON'), (u'Coldwell', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Banker', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Real', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Estate', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'June', u'DATE'), (u'$', u'MONEY'), (u'140,000', u'MONEY'), (u'1914', u'DATE'), (u'South', u'LOCATION'), (u'Dakota', u'LOCATION'), (u'one', u'NUMBER'), (u'five', u'DURATION'), (u'months', u'DURATION'), (u'U.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'daily', u'SET'), (u'$', u'MONEY'), (u'119,000.13-year-old', u'MONEY'), (u'Malachi', u'PERSON'), (u'Hemphill', u'PERSON'), (u'April', u'DATE'), (u'dozen', u'NUMBER'), (u'Malachi', u'PERSON'), (u'Nasir', u'PERSON'), (u'Hemphill', u'PERSON'), (u'Forest', u'LOCATION'), (u'Park', u'LOCATION'), (u'Georgia', u'LOCATION'), (u'13-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Hemphill', u'PERSON'), (u'9', u'NUMBER'), (u'Kershaw', u'LOCATION'), (u'County', u'LOCATION'), (u'South', u'LOCATION'), (u'Carolina', u'LOCATION'), (u'21-year-old', u'DURATION'), (u'Christopher', u'PERSON'), (u'Cravets', u'PERSON'), (u'several', u'DURATION'), (u'hours', u'DURATION'), (u'Charles', u'PERSON'), (u'Belcher', u'PERSON'), (u'Belcher', u'PERSON'), (u'time', u'DATE'), (u'Explorer', u'MISC'), (u'Belcher', u'PERSON'), (u'first', u'ORDINAL'), (u'one', u'NUMBER'), (u'Western', u'LOCATION'), (u'District', u'LOCATION'), (u'of', u'LOCATION'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'Carolina', u'LOCATION'), (u'83', u'NUMBER'), (u'United', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Blood', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Nation', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'September', u'DATE'), (u'2009', u'DATE'), (u'2017', u'DATE'), (u'Hurricane', u'PERSON'), (u'Irma', u'PERSON'), (u'Georgia', u'LOCATION'), (u'National', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Hurricane', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Center', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Irma', u'PERSON'), (u'Charlotte', u'LOCATION'), (u'45', u'NUMBER'), (u'62', u'NUMBER'), (u'18', u'NUMBER'), (u'Charlotte', u'LOCATION'), (u'Cleveland', u'LOCATION'), (u'County', u'LOCATION'), (u'three', u'NUMBER'), (u'`', u'MISC'), (u'Old', u'MISC'), (u'Faithful', u'MISC'), (u'every', u'SET'), (u'90', u'SET'), (u'minutes', u'SET'), (u'Yellowstone', u'LOCATION'), (u'National', u'LOCATION'), (u'Park', u'LOCATION'), (u'Wyoming', u'LOCATION'), (u'June', u'DATE'), (u'1', u'DATE'), (u',', u'DATE'), (u'2011', u'DATE'), (u'MARK', u'PERSON'), (u'RALSTON', u'PERSON'), (u'2011', u'DATE'), (u'March', u'DATE'), (u'1', u'DATE'), (u',', u'DATE'), (u'1872', u'DATE'), (u'Yellowstone', u'LOCATION'), (u'National', u'LOCATION'), (u'Park', u'LOCATION'), (u'first', u'ORDINAL'), (u'year', u'DURATION'), (u'4', u'NUMBER'), (u'million', u'NUMBER'), (u'3,472', u'NUMBER'), (u'three', u'NUMBER'), (u'Idaho', u'LOCATION'), (u'Montana', u'LOCATION'), (u'Yellowstone', u'LOCATION'), (u'2017', u'DATE')]","[u'Charlotte', u'Waxhaw', u'Lake', u'Norman', u'Charlotte', u'Douglas', u'International', u'Airport', u'Georgia', u'Newton', u'County', u'South', u'Dakota', u'U.S.', u'Forest', u'Park', u'Georgia', u'Kershaw', u'County', u'South', u'Carolina', u'Western', u'District', u'of', u'North', u'Carolina', u'Georgia', u'Charlotte', u'Charlotte', u'Cleveland', u'County', u'Yellowstone', u'National', u'Park', u'Wyoming', u'Yellowstone', u'National', u'Park', u'Idaho', u'Montana', u'Yellowstone']"
